DEVIN T. CURRIE

Front-End and UI Developer

Devin is...

Focused on front-end web development specializing in sleek and intuitive user interfaces. Able to produce web sites, applications and interfaces.

Comfortable working directly or remotely with designers, back-end developers and project managers.

Capable of using a variety of languages, frameworks and libraries, and able to adapt to new ones.

SKILLS & EXPERTISE

Front-End Development

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Angular, Node, Express, Mongoose, Mongo, Python, Django, C#, .NET

Project Management

Git, GitHub, GitLab, Subversion, Mercurial, LDAP, FTP/SFTP, Webex, Skype, Gmail, Exchange, XMPP, Office

General

Communications (Written, Oral, Mass, Organizational, Data/ Information), Writing, Social-Media

EXPERIENCE

TransCirrus

October 2014 - Present

UI Developer

Designing and implementing web interfaces on top of Open-Stack.

Freelance

January 2014 - Present

Front-End Developer

Produce web sites and applications working alongside designers and back-end developers.

EDUCATION

Coastal Carolina University

2007-2011

Bachelor of Arts Communications

REFERENCES

Jonathan Arrance

CTO TransCirrus - Employer

jonathan.arrance@transcirrus.com

Brett Dolecheck

Sr. Developer - Manager

brett.dolecheck@transcirrus.com

Barbara Astrini

Designer - Collaborator

barbaraastrini@gmail.com

devintcurrie@gmail.com devintcurrie.com 843-907-1121